<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Stephen Dotz</title><link>https://stephendotz.com/</link><description>Recent content on Stephen Dotz</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://stephendotz.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Stop-Motion Videos Using FFmpeg</title><link>https://stephendotz.com/posts/stop-motion-video-ffmpeg/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://stephendotz.com/posts/stop-motion-video-ffmpeg/</guid><description>Winter is here and my morning project was to swap a set of bindings onto a new snowboard. That&amp;rsquo;s pretty mundane but I decided I would make a stop motion video of the process.
I set the scene up with my iPhone on a tripod and began snapping a picture at every step. I ended with a 52 photo series. The remaining work was to stitch the photos together in a video.</description></item><item><title>Github Actions Will Devour The CI World</title><link>https://stephendotz.com/posts/github-actions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2019 17:53:11 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://stephendotz.com/posts/github-actions/</guid><description>Github Actions is a game changer. I think we are about to see an unprecedented move to Actions as the continuous integration tool of choice. Its convenience and tight integration with GitHub means developers will be jumping into CI for the first time, and adding CI automation in places where previously they might not have bothered to. From a technical standpoint, there is a lot to like about actions. Organizations that are on GitHub cloud or moving there will appeciated the tightly integrated CI tool.</description></item><item><title>Apache Kafka at The New York Times</title><link>https://stephendotz.com/posts/kafka-at-nyt/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 12:10:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://stephendotz.com/posts/kafka-at-nyt/</guid><description>My Colleague Michael Kaminski and I had the pleasure of speaking at the Kafka Meetup hosted at DataDog HQ in NYC.
We shared some of our learnings running Apache Kafka as part of The New York Times’s publishing infrastructure.
We have an atypical use case for Kafka, and seeing it applied in such a unique way seemed to really entertain the audience, and brought out a lot of great questions.</description></item><item><title>A Dev Environment On Your Phone</title><link>https://stephendotz.com/posts/pocket-dev/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 22:50:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://stephendotz.com/posts/pocket-dev/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m editing some Go code in nvim, with syntax highlighting, autocomplete, and ability to build and run, on my iPhone X. The iPhone is running an iOS terminal app using the Mosh protocol to connect to my laptop at home over the cellular network. I have access to all the same things that I would use if I were working normally. I can code, test, commit and push code as usual, and use all of my pre-configured toolchains like kubectl and gcloud.</description></item><item><title>Apple News Push API Client and Command Line Tool</title><link>https://stephendotz.com/posts/apple-news-push-api/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 10:58:56 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://stephendotz.com/posts/apple-news-push-api/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve just open sourced a library for interacting with the Apple News Push API. For those who are unfamiliar, Apple News is an iOS app by Apple that made its debut at Apple&amp;rsquo;s Worldwide Developer Conference (WWDC) in 2015 with the release of iOS 9. It has been pre-installed on all iOS versions since then (Much like calculator, or calendar)
Apple News is a bit different from most newsreader apps. It&amp;rsquo;s not based on RSS or web scraping.</description></item><item><title>Hi, I&#39;m Stephen</title><link>https://stephendotz.com/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stephendotz.com/about/</guid><description>I manage the Publishing Pipeline team at The New York Times. We architect APIs and tooling to help product teams harness the full breadth of NYT&amp;rsquo;s published content in their apps and sites.
Currently I&amp;rsquo;m working with
Google Cloud Platform Kubernetes Go Java gRPC Protocol Buffers Apache Kafka I&amp;rsquo;m interested in technology, programming, coffee, futurism, and modern web architecture.</description></item></channel></rss>